pushys.com.au 2018-09-05

# Pushys Privacy Policy

Pushys is committed to providing goods and services in accordance with all privacy regulations, including the GDPR and the Australian Privacy Act. Any information we collect from you will only be used for the purposes of conducting our business, improving our site, supplying you with our products and services and keeping you informed about aspects of our business that may be of interest to you. 

We will not disclose, sell or lend your personal information to other companies or persons who are not part of our business group, unless we obtain your prior permission. 

## Personal Information

This information is only used for processing orders placed by you and for informing you of products, promotions and services we offer. You have the right to make a request to access the personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. 

## Order Information

When you place an order with us, whether as a registered customer or guest, we collect and keep the following personal information for the purposes of securely verifying and fulfilling your order. 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone number
  * Email address
  * IP address
  * Fraud detection information

All information is stored securely in our internal systems, all of which comply with the GDPR. If you have any questions about the accuracy and security of this information please contact us. 

## Payment Information

We use a secure payment processing system supplied by Braintree for processing credit card and PayPal payments and we do not have access to or store credit card numbers. 

We also offer a Direct deposit payment method and while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot insure or warrant the security of any information you transmit via email or customer response forms. 

## Emails

The use of personal information includes, but is not limited to, sending emails to keep you informed of the status of your order. 

You might also be prompted to subscribe to our newsletters and special offers but the decision for opting in or opting out to receive these newsletters is entirely up to your discretion. We respect your rights to not receive these communications and if you advise us of this we will adjust your account accordingly. Every newsletter we send includes a clear link to unsubscribe in the footer and once unsubscribed you will no longer receive them unless you re-subscribe at a later date. 

## Consent

As required by GDPR residents of the EU will never receive any marketing or similar communication unless they specifically consent and subscribe to our email marketing. 

## Data Security

All personal information submitted on Pushys.com.au is secured using the latest Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) premium encryption technology. Protecting your privacy and personal information is of the highest importance to us and we have systems in place to prevent unauthorised access to and disclosure of your personal information. 

## Cookies & Analytics

As you browse our site a state of the art ecommerce personalisation tool uses first party cookies (which means you are not tracked across websites) and similar technologies to collect anonymous information regarding your use of the site. This information includes the products you viewed and pages you visited, products you added to cart or purchased and general information such as city level location and device type. 

The information is used to provide you with a better experience by showing product recommendations and offers which are relevant you. When you enter your email [and first name], if you choose to allow us to contact you, this tool will receive your email address and may send you personalized offers, reminders and recommendations. 

If you do not access the website for a period longer than 6 months, your email associated with your cookie will be deleted. Your email will never be transferred to anyone else or used for other purposes. You can choose to opt-out from receiving the types of communications referred to above, by following the ‘unsubscribe’ link in the footer in each such communication. 

We also use Google Analytics which utilises cookies for the purpose of analysing the use and behaviour of visitors to our site. None of the information available to us is personally identifiable and you may disable cookies at any time to avoid this type of tracking.  
Detailed information is available at: [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=au)

Social Media plugins like Facebook may also track usage via cookies.

## Policy Updates

We may at our discretion update or revise this privacy policy at any time. Any changes will take effect immediately once they are posted on our website. Your continued use of our services after any changes have been posted on our websites indicates your acceptance to those changes.
